[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In White Men Cant Jump, Sidney Deane, played by Wesley Snipes is married to Rosie Perez character, Gloria Clemente.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these books about prehistoric animals and dinosaurs was written by Arthur Conan Doyle?", "correct_answer": "The Lost World", "incorrect_answers": ["Dinosaur Planet", "Jurassic Park", "Dinotopia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When performing a routine blood draw, the basilic vein is the best choice.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which side effect is not related to the use of marijuana?", "correct_answer": "Violent behaviour", "incorrect_answers": ["Silly and causeless giggling", "Red, bloodshot eyes", "Dizziness and staggering"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The color called pistachio is a shade of this general color.", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown", "Red", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Catfish are bony fish that are active in the nighttime. How did they get their interesting name?", "correct_answer": "They have barbels that remind of cat whiskers.", "incorrect_answers": ["They like to rub against objects like cats do.", "They have cat eyes.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the former profession of Leonard, the main character in Memento?", "correct_answer": "He used to be an insurance fraud investigator.", "incorrect_answers": ["He used to be a priest.", "He used to be a cop.", "He used to be teacher."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a popular 1960s slogan, where would you meet the nicest people?", "correct_answer": "On a Honda", "incorrect_answers": ["At the AMC theaters", "At Macys", "In Las Vegas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is in Central Europe?", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Bulgaria", "Portugal", "Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ethel and Norman Thayer were Oscar-winning roles in this 1981 drama.", "correct_answer": "On Golden Pond", "incorrect_answers": ["The English Patient", "Crash", "Network"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Freddys daughters first name?", "correct_answer": "Kathryn", "incorrect_answers": ["Krystal", "Kristina", "Carol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Male Tomato Frogs are bright red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]